Obviously,
the business continuity plan needs to be
maintained somewhere where it can be accessed
often in modern organizations,
everything is digital and not provided as a hard copy.
This can be dangerous just like storing
everything within the main company building.
Some organizations have what is called the red book,
which is given to the appropriate individual outside the facility.
All the procedures are outlined in that document
in case for example, a hurricane hits
the power is out and all the facilities are
compromised and there is no access to electronic backups.
It is important to update this hard copy red
book any time the electronic copy is updated.
So both versions remain consistent.